<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MVICore Demo</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="action_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="drawer_main">Main</string>
    <string name="drawer_lifecycle">Lifecycle</string>
    <string name="settings_show_toasts">Toasts</string>

    <string name="help_dialog_main">
    <![CDATA[
        <h2>UI controls</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>Tap the colored boxes to set selection.</li>
            <li>Tap the FAB icon to increase counter. </li>
            <li>Tap the cat image to load another image (async). </li>
            <li>Tap TOASTS to show/hide fake analytics toast messages for UI interactions. This is to demonstrate time travel replay channels (more on that below)</li>
            <li>Tap SIGN OUT and SIGN IN again to see how destroying the scope resets the state. </li>
        </ul>

        <h2>Errors</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>The \'Simulated error was triggered\' toast fires randomly when loading the image to demonstrate event handling. Check <b>Feature2</b> for that.</li>
        </ul>

        <h2>Time travel how-to</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>Slide with your finger from the right edge of the screen to open DebugDrawer (close this dialog first). </li>
            <li>You can record interaction with the UI then replay it. Don\'t forget to stop recording first :) </li>
        </ul>

        <h2>Time travel channels</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>You can select replay channel in the dropdown. To replay everything on the UI, select <b>MainActivity.ViewModels</b> channel. </li>
            <li>Notice how the \'Simulated error was triggered\' error message doesn\'t replay on the <b>MainActivity.ViewModels</b> channel (it\'s not part of the state), but you can replay it on the <b>MainActivity.News</b> channel</li>
            <li>You can select to replay only <b>Feature1</b> (counter and colored boxes) or only <b>Feature2</b> (async image loading) internal channels and see what happens on the UI.</li>
            <li>Tap TOASTS to turn on showing fake analytics toast messages for UI interactions. See how they are replayed on the <b>MainActivity.Analytics</b> channel, even if the toasts were originally turned off when you made the recording. </li>
        </ul>

        <h2>Points of interest in the source code</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>MainActivityBindings</b> for reactive bindings</li>
            <li><b>Feature1</b> for basic example</li>
            <li><b>Feature2</b> for async loading and event handling (\'Simulated error was triggered\' toast is an event and not part of the state)</li>
        </ul>

        <h2>Retaining state</h2>
            <li>Rotate the device to see that the state is persisted (sorry for ugly landscape layout). </li>
            <li>Tap SIGN OUT and SIGN IN again to see how destroying the scope resets the state. </li>
        </ul>
    ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
